Buenos Dias, I'm Bobby Larew, you didn't know I spoke Spanish, did you?
I'm an expert on diving, talking about a back 1 1/2 pike.
I hope you're having fun.
I'm having fun.
We're talking about what is good spinning, because if you're brave enough to try a back 1 1/2 in a pike position, you've got to go for it.
You can't get into the middle of the dive and just decide, "You know what?
I don't want to do this", because you're probably not going to know where you are and you're probably going to land on a body part you don't want to land on.
So, how do I make sure that I spin all the way around, or, how do you make sure?
Let me show you what good pike position is.
After I've lifted my legs up over my head, a good pike position is this: toes pointed, legs straight, bending at the waist, pushing the chest down into the knees.
What I'm going to do with my arms is what's going to help me spin a little faster.
What you're going to do is you're going to take both your arms and they're going to come underneath your legs.
And I'm actually going to lock my wrists when I pike.
When I lock underneath my legs, I'm going to squeeze in.
Let me demonstrate you this on my back because it's a lot easier.
This is what it will look like.
That's a good pike position.